<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Undergrad on cassie.ink</title>
    <link>https://example.org/tags/undergrad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Undergrad on cassie.ink</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/tags/undergrad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LITR 308 Emily Dickinson &amp; Queer Theory</title>
      <link>https://example.org/emily-dickinson-queer-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/emily-dickinson-queer-theory/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The lives of many literary greats remain a relative mystery; literary critics and historians are often left to piece together details from letters, documentation, and, sometimes controversially, the author&amp;rsquo;s work read for repeated motifs. They then draw what conclusions they can about the authors&amp;rsquo; lives. One of the most prolific female poets in the English literary canon, Emily Dickinson&amp;rsquo;s life is preserved in letters and artifacts from her life. When examined as a body of work, Dickinson&amp;rsquo;s poetry reveals a pattern of focus on women&amp;rsquo;s interior lives and relationships that may be regarded as queer, especially with the added dimension of her close relationship with her sister-in-law. This essay examines a selection of her poems through a queer lens, highlighting the poems&amp;rsquo; relationships to female love and Dickinson&amp;rsquo;s life and arguing against established patterns of erasing Dickinson&amp;rsquo;s queer identity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LITR 250 Close Reading 2E</title>
      <link>https://example.org/litr-250-close-reading-2e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/litr-250-close-reading-2e/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the beginning of Chapter VIII in the third section of &lt;em&gt;To the Lighthouse&lt;/em&gt;, pages 186-187, Virginia Woolf&amp;rsquo;s unique approach to perspective and introspection create a subjective presentation of reality and relationships, supported by extended metaphors of fluidity and stillness. On a boat trip mandated by Mr. Ramsay to the titular lighthouse, Cam and James anatomize and unfold their feelings towards their father. Cam evolves as the boat moves across the sea while James&amp;rsquo;s unflinching rage and violence towards the patriarch repeat in this section as the sailboat halts and space contracts to exacerbate his indignation. Woolf thus frames and explores the figure of Mr. Ramsay and the nominal motif of a journey through individual introspection and excurses. &lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
