<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Media-Log on cassie.ink</title>
    <link>https://example.org/tags/media-log/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Media-Log on cassie.ink</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/tags/media-log/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Media Log (January 2024)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/media-log-2024-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/media-log-2024-01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tv&#34;&gt;TV&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;One Tree Hill&lt;/em&gt;, season six and seven&lt;/strong&gt; - I&amp;rsquo;ve been marathoning One Tree Hill on a friend&amp;rsquo;s recommendation. By this season, we are well passed the &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo; seasons, but it&amp;rsquo;s still entertaining enough to watch — if only to count how many more car crashes the writers will introduce as plot lines. I think the early (1-4) seasons are a decent watch, but at this point, I&amp;rsquo;m really just seeing it through to the end. Season seven has a novelty in seeing how a show pivots after losing its main character. I don&amp;rsquo;t think &lt;em&gt;OTH&lt;/em&gt; did so gracefully; they elevated some, generously, background characters into the main act and lumped on bunch of new ones at that. Some work better than others, but at least I&amp;rsquo;m almost at the end.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kitchen Nightmares&lt;/em&gt; (2023)&lt;/strong&gt; - Years ago, I once came home to find my partner watching &lt;em&gt;Kitchen Nightmares&lt;/em&gt; on YouTube. He&amp;rsquo;s generally not a fan of reality or competition shows, so I asked him why he was watching it. He giggled and said, &amp;ldquo;He [Gordon] just gets so mad.&amp;rdquo; That led to me also watching a bunch of the show. This month I watched a gabi belle video in which she talked about the reboot, so I dipped in too. Gordon does indeed still get mad. When watching &lt;em&gt;Kitchen Nightmares&lt;/em&gt;, I am always thinking of how much fun the show must be to edit. The editors make liberal use of the most unhinged sound effects imaginable. It&amp;rsquo;s junk food TV, and who doesn&amp;rsquo;t love junk food?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Schitt&amp;rsquo;s Creek&lt;/strong&gt; - I&amp;rsquo;ve been casually rewatching as my background noise / take a nap on the couch TV. Still hilarious and as good as the first time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bachelor&lt;/strong&gt; - Two of my friends are big fans, so I&amp;rsquo;m watching the current season with them. I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen any &lt;em&gt;Bachelor&lt;/em&gt; properties before this; I&amp;rsquo;m mostly along for the ride. The show has yet to hit the reality TV highs that keep me looped in to shows like &lt;em&gt;America&amp;rsquo;s Next Top Model&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Survivor&lt;/em&gt;, and the whole concept still feels quite skeezy to me.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;music&#34;&gt;Music&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;III&lt;/em&gt;, The Lumineers&lt;/strong&gt; - I have liked some of The Lumineers&amp;rsquo; hits for years, but a friend really loves them, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d give &lt;em&gt;III&lt;/em&gt; a shot. I understand it&amp;rsquo;s a concept album with stories and characters; I really haven&amp;rsquo;t delved into that. I&amp;rsquo;m unsure if that&amp;rsquo;s because I haven&amp;rsquo;t found it compelling or because I am trying to focus more on the &lt;em&gt;sound&lt;/em&gt; rather than just the words (I&amp;rsquo;ve always been more for the latter). &lt;em&gt;III&lt;/em&gt; sounds great; it reminds me of how much I love the piano. It&amp;rsquo;s the focal point of many songs on the album but also beautifully interspersed as a twinkly highlight or backdrop. Particular favorites are &amp;ldquo;Donna&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;My Cell.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Log (August 2023)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/media-log-august-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/media-log-august-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;movies&#34;&gt;Movies&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Barbie&lt;/em&gt; - I was underwhelmed. There&amp;rsquo;s been lots of chatter, and I loved &lt;em&gt;Lady Bird&lt;/em&gt;, but &lt;em&gt;Barbie&lt;/em&gt; didn&amp;rsquo;t hit for me; too much Ken (to be the hundredth person to whine about it) and the ending felt unearned and thematically confused. This was more of an homage to &lt;em&gt;Barbie&lt;/em&gt; as a product than it was an homage to womanhood, but it pretended to be the latter.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;games&#34;&gt;Games&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Vampire Survivors&lt;/em&gt; - I originally played &lt;em&gt;Vampire Survivors&lt;/em&gt; for my video game podcast, &lt;a href=&#34;https://pitchandplay.org&#34;&gt;Pitch &amp;amp; Play&lt;/a&gt; (on hiatus but will come back!); my friend and co-host Ross recommended it to me. I was pleasantly surprised by how much I got into it given that I don&amp;rsquo;t really have nostalgia for this sort of game, but I played several hours of it and then became distracted by life. While moving this month, I was without internet for quite a while and had not hooked up my consoles (or my PC, still). To kill some time while my body recovered from lifting boxes and scrubbing surfaces, I downloaded &lt;em&gt;Vampire Survivors&lt;/em&gt; onto my phone and went deep into it. It&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic game that I&amp;rsquo;ll come to associate with my early days in the house.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;books&#34;&gt;Books&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Walk Two Moons&lt;/em&gt; by Sharon Creech - I read this book originally as a child in the fifth grade. I remember loving it but little else. I have been looking for a text to add to my curriculum and wanted to try &lt;em&gt;Walk Two Moons&lt;/em&gt; out. I enjoyed reading it and was surprised by how much of it came back to me even though I am (nearly) twenty years out from reading it the first time. I do think the Native American set dressing might be problematic given that the author is not, by any account I&amp;rsquo;ve read, actually Native; the plot is also predictable, but perhaps that is because I&amp;rsquo;m an adult reading a book written for children and because I&amp;rsquo;ve read it before. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure it&amp;rsquo;s the book I&amp;rsquo;m looking for, but it&amp;rsquo;s not a bad read.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Log (July 2023)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/media-log-july-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/media-log-july-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Part of my resolution to blog more is to start a media consumption log for the year where I record what I’m reading, watching, and listening to. I&amp;rsquo;m going to do it monthly; expect a finalized list on the last day of each month (possibly backdated).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;movies&#34;&gt;Movies&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Fast and the Furious&lt;/em&gt; - a rewatch of a movie I watched way too much as a child and therefore have an unreasonable fondness and attachment towards. The dialogue in this movie is positively absurd (“I like the tuna here,&amp;quot; “Welcome to Race Wars”), the homoerotic undertones bordering on overtones, and everyone in this movie (except Vince but including Jesse) is blisteringly hot. I was edified by the friend I had watched the film (not movie) with, who had never seen it, as she remarked at the end, “I get it now.” I could have done without the oil scene, however.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;2 Fast 2 Furious&lt;/em&gt; – well, now it’s a marathon. &lt;em&gt;2 Fast 2 Furious&lt;/em&gt; has, historically and controversially, been both my favorite sequel naming schema and overall entry in the &lt;em&gt;Fast&lt;/em&gt; saga. I love the first, but this movie embraces the stupidity and over-the-top action that would go on to define the series. It manages to succeed without Vin Diesel (or any of the “family,” except for Brian, though it introduces future members) and contains some iconic (to me) scenes (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dpwl45hUQfc&amp;amp;pp=ygUMZWplY3RvIHNlYXRv&#34;&gt;Ejecto seato&lt;/a&gt; and everything involving Suki). I smile constantly while watching this movie. I love it and I think it loves me back. Except for the rat scene. I could do without the rat scene.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Fast and the Furious: Tokyo Drift&lt;/em&gt; – I would like to say that I came to my second viewing of this movie with an open mind (I didn’t), hoping to understand the cultural revisionism of some &lt;em&gt;Fast&lt;/em&gt; fans who claim that this is actually one of the best in the series (it isn’t). Somehow this movie makes drifting boring. Han is the only interesting character. There’s a character who everyone refers to as “DK” (short for “Drift King”) throughout the film and yet he is as bland and forgettable as the rest. Sean is the worst, and it is a miracle the series managed to rebound from this low. &lt;em&gt;Tokyo Drift&lt;/em&gt; is the ugly step-cousin of the &lt;em&gt;Fast&lt;/em&gt; series. At least the theme song slaps.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fast &amp;amp; Furious&lt;/em&gt; – viewed right after &lt;em&gt;Tokyo Drift&lt;/em&gt; to cleanse my palate and remind me what a good movie feels like. The opening scene immediately reminds one of the highs of the &lt;em&gt;Fast&lt;/em&gt; saga, and while the rest of the movie is far from the best, it is miles ahead of &lt;em&gt;Tokyo Drift&lt;/em&gt;, if only because it reunites the &lt;em&gt;Fast&lt;/em&gt; family and sets the pieces in place for the highs of the series to come.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fast Five&lt;/em&gt; – a truly thrilling movie start to finish and perhaps the best of the series. Everything about this movie is fun — no rat or oil scenes to be found. Instead, just action sequences that constantly raise the stakes and delight — and, of course, the reunion of the family (sans-Letty).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fast &amp;amp; Furious 6&lt;/em&gt; – a middling sequel to the high point of the &lt;em&gt;Fast&lt;/em&gt; series and my last rewatch; from here on out, it is all new to me. This one is watchable and certainly ranks as one of the better &lt;em&gt;Fast&lt;/em&gt; movies. It chases the ragtag quality that the family had in the last movie but doesn’t hit the same notes. The movie shines when it focuses on Dom and Letty’s relationship, and the bridge scene is one of the best stupid stunts in the series.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Furious 7&lt;/em&gt; – a mostly forgettable setup and plot offset by some truly ridiculous moments that make the film, overall, enjoyable. This was a classy send-off for Paul Walker that I’m sure was emotional in the moment but is today soured by him being kind of a creep. I wish to wed the individual who came up with the Rock breaking his cast off and entering the action, the skyscraper scene, Dom running over Shaw&amp;rsquo;s car, and, most of all, the rwrench fight. I say individual because I like to believe there is a single person responsible for this lunacy.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;tv&#34;&gt;TV&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Andor&lt;/em&gt;, season one – interesting in broad strokes, but I found it deeply problematic on an episode-to-episode basis. This felt like a movie trilogy that decided to be a television show, and it does not work as either. It may not be fair for me to levy my frustrations with cinematic universes against &lt;em&gt;Andor&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;em&gt;Fast&lt;/em&gt; obsession notwithstanding), but I spent much of my time with the show questioning its necessity (even as a &lt;em&gt;Star Wars&lt;/em&gt; lover and a particular fan of &lt;em&gt;Rogue One&lt;/em&gt;). Much of &lt;em&gt;Andor&lt;/em&gt; felt like it was undercutting &lt;em&gt;Rogue One&lt;/em&gt; and Jyn’s significance to the Alliance. &lt;em&gt;Andor&lt;/em&gt; has compelling ideas and is competently shot and acted, with occasionally strong moments every few episodes, but it ultimately didn’t win me over. I will give a second season a try, but &lt;em&gt;Andor&lt;/em&gt; disappointed me, especially given the high expectations others’ reactions gave me.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;music&#34;&gt;Music&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;22, a Million&lt;/em&gt;, Bon Iver – I do not have much experience with Bon Iver outside of “Skinny Love” (which is fine), but I vaguely recall my sister playing me a song, “10 d E A T h b R E a s T ⚄ ⚄”, from_ 22, a Million_ around when it came out. Sparked by a recent conversation with her and stumbling across an article that I now cannot find about some of the controversy around the album’s release, I’ve been listening to it a fair amount. It’s an abstract, exciting album; none of the songs particularly stand out to me as Playlist Material, but that is perhaps the intention of the album: it is to be listened to in sittings, full through, not in the vacuum we have become accustomed to of random shuffles and algorithmic picks. I admire any artist that experiments with their releases and does not rest on the laurels of their hits, so initial impressions are strong, but I get the sense that this is an album that begs for the listener to reflect and decode.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Never Hungover Again&lt;/em&gt;, Joyce Manor – discovered through a Front Bottoms shuffle with “Heart Tattoo,” which is a highlight of the album for me. Never Hungover Again is a breezy listen: ten tracks, most falling between one and two minutes. I found the first five tracks mostly discardable, but the second half was much stronger with the aforementioned “Heart Tattoo,” “In the Army Now,” and “Catalina Fight Song.” Emo revival works best for me in The Front Bottoms style: catchy riffs and earnest lyrics that read like teenage LiveJournal entries.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;games&#34;&gt;Games&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom&lt;/em&gt; - I played a metric ton of &lt;em&gt;Breath of the Wild&lt;/em&gt; and emerged with feelings ranging from ambivalent to frustrated. There was so much I loved about it and so much that just never came together (or actively frustrated me). &lt;em&gt;Tears of the Kingdom,&lt;/em&gt; however, has brought me nothing but joy; it corrects every complaint I had with &lt;em&gt;Breath of the Wild&lt;/em&gt; and improves upon it wholesale. I&amp;rsquo;m far from done with the game &amp;ndash; I think I will be playing it for some time &amp;ndash; but so far, it is remarkable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Taco Cat Goat Cheese Pizza&lt;/em&gt; - played with friends but I had the eerie suspicion I&amp;rsquo;ve played it before but cannot place it. Fine in a group but mostly forgettable. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t seek it out again.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Carcassonne&lt;/em&gt; - my love, my liege. &lt;em&gt;Carcassonne&lt;/em&gt; is a bastion in our household. I love it every time I play, except when I lose, which is often.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Busy Bistro&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://magicpuzzlecompany.com/&#34;&gt;Magic Puzzle Company&lt;/a&gt; - a friend spotted this on Tik Tok and invited me over to work on it with her. Reader, I was there until three in the morning. A fantastic puzzle with charming art, done in good company.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
