<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on cassie.ink</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on cassie.ink</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on elections</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reflections-on-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reflections-on-elections/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2016 was the first year I was eligible to vote in a presidential election. I was away at college, so I completed an absentee ballot, and, like most, felt confident in what I thought would be the result. I was no big fan of Clinton&amp;rsquo;s — I voted for Bernie in the primaries — but the other option was laughable: I couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe that a major political party put such a clown up as their candidate, and I thought the electorate was smart enough to see him for the fraud (and fascist) he was.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>smooth runs the water where the brook is deep</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/smooth-runs-the-water-where-the-brook-is-deep/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/smooth-runs-the-water-where-the-brook-is-deep/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Write a blog post about words of wisdom your younger self would have appreciated hearing.&#xA;(via &lt;a href=&#34;https://blogprompts.fyi&#34;&gt;blogprompts&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m trying out doing blog prompts in an effort to populate this blog with more than just weekly round-ups and to get more comfortable writing about personal things.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:2&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m going to select two quotes — both song lyrics — that have resonated for me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first is from &amp;ldquo;Banshee Beat&amp;rdquo; by Animal Collective, which I first heard in my late teens (maybe 16?) and still consider one of my favorite songs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving to a rack mount setup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/moving-to-a-rack-mount-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/moving-to-a-rack-mount-setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wrote a post a few months ago &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/moving-my-home-server-to-a-new-chassis/&#34;&gt;cataloguing moving my home server&lt;/a&gt; from the old NZXT case I had leftover from my old PC into a Rosewill chassis that would let me, eventually, move to a proper rack setup. This past Prime Day, I purchased a Riveco 15U rack and then some sliding rails to go along with it, with the hope of finally moving the loud and hot NAS into the basement where it belongs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>breaking silences</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/breaking-silences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/breaking-silences/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/your-silence-will-not-protect-you/&#34;&gt;Last time I updated this blog&lt;/a&gt;, I wrote about silences in my professional career. These past few weeks, I feel I am doing the work to break mine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am the faculty advisor for my middle school&amp;rsquo;s GSA. I have been for years now, and it&amp;rsquo;s something I&amp;rsquo;m very proud of, but this year especially I feel I have a great crop of kids that I&amp;rsquo;m really connecting with. At my town&amp;rsquo;s Pride festival in early June, my club had a booth selling crafts the kids had made to raise funds. The kids filtered in and out to help sell goods, but mostly I think they just valued having a &amp;ldquo;home base&amp;rdquo; at the event. For me, it was a long, socially draining day, but speaking to them afterward about the experience and hearing them tell me how at home they felt at the festival, how comfortable they felt being themselves, was so gratifying.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your silence will not protect you</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/your-silence-will-not-protect-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/your-silence-will-not-protect-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve talked before on this blog about &lt;a href=&#34;../on-teaching/&#34;&gt;being a teacher&lt;/a&gt; and how passionate I am about my work; the time I spend with my students — which should be paramount and where all my energy goes — comes naturally. I often remark that I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m doing a stand-up comedy routine&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; while teaching because my goal is not only to instruct but to develop joy in learning, in reading, in writing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving my home server to a new chassis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/moving-my-home-server-to-a-new-chassis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/moving-my-home-server-to-a-new-chassis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have a home server (running Unraid) that I use to backup computers, as media storage, and to run various apps. It&amp;rsquo;s mostly been cobbled together from used parts I found for cheap, and it generally followed &lt;a href=&#34;https://forums.serverbuilds.net/t/guide-nas-killer-4-0-fast-quiet-power-efficient-and-flexible-starting-at-125/667&#34;&gt;Serverbuild&amp;rsquo;s NAS Killer 4 guide&lt;/a&gt;. It runs like a dream, and putting it together is one of the best decisions I&amp;rsquo;ve ever made. More recently, with streaming sites like Netflix, Hulu, etc. cracking down on password sharing, it has become my pathway to shedding some monthly subscriptions and owning my own media.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thirteen to Know Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thirteen-to-know-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thirteen-to-know-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@jamesmckz &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jamesmckz/status/1764778536244507081&#34;&gt;shared the following challenge on X&lt;/a&gt; earlier this month:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No cheating - your Quietus style Bakers Dozen. 13 albums (off the top of your head) to know you by. Not looking for a perfect list, looking for a list that you instantly regret posting because you then remember something else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I approached my response largely as a list of albums that have meant something to me in my life — not necessarily what I&amp;rsquo;m actively listening to at the moment. Many of these albums I&amp;rsquo;ve not listened to much in years, but I consider them pivotal, essential listening for &lt;em&gt;me&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/coming-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/coming-out/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I read a thread online recently about bisexuality: folks were discussing use of the label compared to something like pansexual. Many folks within the LGBTQ+ umbrella argue that pansexual is a more inclusive label than bisexual, as &lt;em&gt;bi-&lt;/em&gt; upholds a binary view of gender.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My relationship with my bisexuality has been fraught. I can pinpoint in specificity where I feel it started: in the sixth grade (for me, 2005 or 2006), reading the sex ed chapter in my science textbook, I was presented with the three sexualities — heterosexuality, homosexuality, and bisexuality. I had, by that point, already started puberty and experienced low-level attraction. I&amp;rsquo;d been confused that that attraction never seemed to have a distinct target: I liked boys and I liked girls. I remember an immediate sense of comfort and belonging in the term. &lt;em&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s allowed?&lt;/em&gt;, I thought. Reading it in a textbook made it seem so simple. &lt;em&gt;Then surely that&amp;rsquo;s the way to be.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hate for the island</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hate-for-the-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hate-for-the-island/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was born and raised on Long Island in a hamlet that rests along the Great South Bay.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Known to most as a ferry town, this charming suburb lives and breathes the ocean. Most every resident has access to some kind of boat, whether through personal ownership or advantageous friendship. In the 90s, the town was voted the &amp;ldquo;friendliest town in America,&amp;rdquo; a slogan that still adorns the sign as you drive into town, by a mysterious group that awards such superlatives. That accolade, along with our yacht clubs, country clubs, lack of racial diversity, and generalized fear of anything outside the norm makes the town the near picture of 1950s suburban ideal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my year in lists</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/my-year-in-lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-year-in-lists/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not a New Years Resolution person; listening to a lot of &lt;a href=&#34;https://loscampesinos.bandcamp.com/track/my-year-in-lists-2&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;My Year in Lists&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt; by Los Campesinos! as a teen made me quite cynical about the whole thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, I &lt;em&gt;am&lt;/em&gt; a very goal-oriented, reflective person. In late 2022, after years of gaining weight and developing some really negative patterns of self-talk around my body image, I decided to join a gym. Of course I&amp;rsquo;d like to see the number on the scale go down, but the main goal was just to get healthier and develop healthier habits. I started running, because that&amp;rsquo;s what I used to do (not well), and eventually convinced a friend to join with me. Together, we set the goal of running a 5K, and we did our first in May of 2023, in about 41 minutes (in our defense, it was an &lt;em&gt;extremely&lt;/em&gt; hilly course, but also progress, progress&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;). We ran three more as the year went by; my most recent was November, where I finished in around 36 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stages of Moving</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/stages-of-moving/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/stages-of-moving/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;stage-1-denial--naivety&#34; class=&#34;anchor&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;a href=&#34;#stage-1-denial--naivety&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;        Stage 1: Denial &amp;amp; Naivety&#xD;&#xA;        &lt;span class=&#34;tooltip&#34;&gt;&lt;svg xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; width=&#34;24&#34; height=&#34;24&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 24 24&#34; fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke=&#34;currentColor&#34; stroke-width=&#34;2&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-linejoin=&#34;round&#34; class=&#34;icon icon-tabler icons-tabler-outline icon-tabler-link&#34;&gt;&lt;path stroke=&#34;none&#34; d=&#34;M0 0h24v24H0z&#34; fill=&#34;none&#34;/&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M9 15l6 -6&#34; /&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M11 6l.463 -.536a5 5 0 0 1 7.071 7.072l-.534 .464&#34; /&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M13 18l-.397 .534a5.068 5.068 0 0 1 -7.127 0a4.972 4.972 0 0 1 0 -7.071l.524 -.463&#34; /&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have that much stuff. I don&amp;rsquo;t think packing is going to be that hard this time. I&amp;rsquo;ve already boxed up my books &amp;ndash; how much more could I need to do?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
