<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on cassie.ink</title>
    <link>https://example.org/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on cassie.ink</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>an ode to gitsync</title>
      <link>https://example.org/an-ode-to-gitsync/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/an-ode-to-gitsync/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since I &lt;a href=&#34;https://cassie.ink/what%27s-this-%28and-how-it-works%29/&#34;&gt;moved this site to Hugo&lt;/a&gt;, I&amp;rsquo;ve been using an app called GitJournal to post from my phone. I have a beautiful desk setup with a clacky mechanical keyboard that&amp;rsquo;s a joy to write on, but the simple fact is that I&amp;rsquo;m a lazy shit and want to update my blog from the couch. It&amp;rsquo;s all mostly worked fine, with some headaches. I originally intended to use GitJournal to store my Github repo to my phone&amp;rsquo;s filesystem and then point an Obsidian&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; vault at that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automattic&#39;s Write Brief is, unsurprisingly, full of shit</title>
      <link>https://example.org/write-brief/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/write-brief/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Automattic &lt;a href=&#34;https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/automattic-launches-ai-writing-tool-that-aims-to-make-wordpress-blogs-more-readable-and-succinct/&#34;&gt;recently launched their Write Brief AI assistant&lt;/a&gt; for folks using Jetpack with WordPress.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; It is automatically available to anyone using wordpress.com, which I verified by logging into my 14-year-old account.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I decided to test it out on my recent post about &lt;em&gt;The Basic Eight&lt;/em&gt;. I chose this because it&amp;rsquo;s one of my more recent posts that isn&amp;rsquo;t #week-notes . I pasted it directly into the Gutenberg editor with all of the AI settings toggled on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving to a rack mount setup</title>
      <link>https://example.org/moving-to-a-rack-mount-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/moving-to-a-rack-mount-setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wrote a post a few months ago &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/moving-my-home-server-to-a-new-chassis/&#34;&gt;cataloguing moving my home server&lt;/a&gt; from the old NZXT case I had leftover from my old PC into a Rosewill chassis that would let me, eventually, move to a proper rack setup. This past Prime Day, I purchased a Riveco 15U rack and then some sliding rails to go along with it, with the hope of finally moving the loud and hot NAS into the basement where it belongs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving my home server to a new chassis</title>
      <link>https://example.org/moving-my-home-server-to-a-new-chassis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/moving-my-home-server-to-a-new-chassis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have a home server (running Unraid) that I use to backup computers, as media storage, and to run various apps. It&amp;rsquo;s mostly been cobbled together from used parts I found for cheap, and it generally followed &lt;a href=&#34;https://forums.serverbuilds.net/t/guide-nas-killer-4-0-fast-quiet-power-efficient-and-flexible-starting-at-125/667&#34;&gt;Serverbuild&amp;rsquo;s NAS Killer 4 guide&lt;/a&gt;. It runs like a dream, and putting it together is one of the best decisions I&amp;rsquo;ve ever made. More recently, with streaming sites like Netflix, Hulu, etc. cracking down on password sharing, it has become my pathway to shedding some monthly subscriptions and owning my own media.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
