<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movies on cassie.ink</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movies on cassie.ink</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Women in a Sea of Men: The Representation of Women in The Curse of the Black Pearl</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/women-in-a-sea-of-men-the-representation-of-women-in-the-curse-of-the-black-pearl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/women-in-a-sea-of-men-the-representation-of-women-in-the-curse-of-the-black-pearl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently, my boyfriend and I decided to revisit a childhood classic: &lt;em&gt;Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl&lt;/em&gt;, the film that jump-started what would prove to be an extremely lucrative and much beloved franchise for Disney. I first watched it not long after its 2003 release, making me 8 or 9 at the time, and enjoyed it, like most other children at the time. It brims with swashbuckling adventure and humor while maintaining Disney’s family-friendly directive. Unfortunately, with my older, more world-weary eyes saw through the dust of nostalgia, dismayed as the film makes no effort to pass the Bechdel-Wallace Test, which stands as an absolute bare minimum requirement for a creative endeavor’s portrayal of women.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Has a Problem with Women and We’re Going to Fix It Together</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/star-wars-has-a-problem-with-women-and-were-going-to-fix-it-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/star-wars-has-a-problem-with-women-and-were-going-to-fix-it-together/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let’s start by making something perfectly clear: I love &lt;em&gt;Star Wars&lt;/em&gt;. I live and breathe &lt;em&gt;Star Wars&lt;/em&gt;. They’re some of my favorite movies, games, and comics; I’ve read more than my fair share of &lt;em&gt;Star Wars&lt;/em&gt; fanfiction and have, over the years, spent a ludicrous amount of money on merchandise and other paraphernalia.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When someone, tasked with buying me a gift, asks for ideas, I give them one instruction: if it has &lt;em&gt;Star Wars&lt;/em&gt; on it, I’ll like it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
