<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Television on cassie.ink</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/television/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Television on cassie.ink</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Princess Bubblegum &amp; Marceline: Still Just Almost Girlfriends</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/princess-bubblegum-marceline-still-just-almost-girlfriends/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/princess-bubblegum-marceline-still-just-almost-girlfriends/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s only natural that the first post on my shiny new blog should be about these two, isn’t it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let me preface this post by saying that I love Princess Bubblegum and Marceline and Bubbline and Sugarless Gum, all of that — whatever you’d like to call it, I ship it. Hard. I may not be a long-time &lt;em&gt;Adventure Time&lt;/em&gt; fan; I have not experienced firsthand the “What Was Missing” controversy, the joy delivered when &lt;em&gt;Sky Witch&lt;/em&gt; premiered, and so on. I jumped on-board late, binge-watched my way to this pairing, which washed over me with all its fluffy, tumultuous grace. I was vaguely aware that it was a popular ship as I made my way up to “What Was Missing”; I transcended as I witnessed Marceline’s impromptu, angst-ridden love ballad to Peebles; I immediately rewatched “Go With Me”, eager to see the pair’s first on-screen interaction; I stormed ahead to “Sky Witch”. I filled my tumblr with all the lovely fanart in existence for the couple, bemusing my followers who already taunted me for my FemShep/Liara obsession; I formed headcanons, all of it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
