<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Literature on cassie.ink</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/literature/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Literature on cassie.ink</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/literature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Climbing my personal Mount Doom (I finished reading Lord of the Rings)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/i-finished-lord-of-the-rings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/i-finished-lord-of-the-rings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Peter Jackson&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring&lt;/em&gt; released in 2001 when I was seven years old. At the time, my media diet consisted mostly of &lt;em&gt;The Powerpuff Girls&lt;/em&gt; and obsessively reading and re-reading the first four &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/em&gt; books.&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; I would like to say that my father was thoughtful and felt that I would have enjoyed another fantasy series with wizards and magic but knew that a three-plus-hour theater experience was tall ask for a seven year old. Unfortunately, I know him, and I think it more likely that he is cheap and thought the movie looked cool, so when &lt;em&gt;Fellowship&lt;/em&gt; released on home media, we trucked to the neighborhood  knock-off and rented it on VHS. That night, I crowded with my two older siblings around a (by today&amp;rsquo;s standards) laughably small tube TV. We tucked in with no expectations or understanding of what the movie would be about.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I finished The Basic Eight and I can&#39;t decide if I enjoyed it</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-basic-eight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-basic-eight/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Spoilers to follow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wrote in my week notes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Basic Eight&lt;/em&gt; by Daniel Handler.&lt;/strong&gt; Handler&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Adverbs&lt;/em&gt; is often what I cite when folks ask what my favorite book is, and I loved &lt;em&gt;Watch Your Mouth&lt;/em&gt;, too. I need light reprieves from &lt;em&gt;The Odyssey&lt;/em&gt;, too, so this seemed an excellent time to round out my reading of Handler&amp;rsquo;s bibliography. I&amp;rsquo;m about halfway through and enraptured by the narrative voice. It&amp;rsquo;s pretentious, as a story narrated by a precocious high school senior should be, without being cloying, and with Handler&amp;rsquo;s charming humor throughout. I love it so far and have faith that the feeling will continue. I normally hate books set in high school, but this one takes me back to my high school self — somehow, in a good way, which I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve ever felt before.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LITR 308 Emily Dickinson &amp; Queer Theory</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/emily-dickinson-queer-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/emily-dickinson-queer-theory/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The lives of many literary greats remain a relative mystery; literary critics and historians are often left to piece together details from letters, documentation, and, sometimes controversially, the author&amp;rsquo;s work read for repeated motifs. They then draw what conclusions they can about the authors&amp;rsquo; lives. One of the most prolific female poets in the English literary canon, Emily Dickinson&amp;rsquo;s life is preserved in letters and artifacts from her life. When examined as a body of work, Dickinson&amp;rsquo;s poetry reveals a pattern of focus on women&amp;rsquo;s interior lives and relationships that may be regarded as queer, especially with the added dimension of her close relationship with her sister-in-law. This essay examines a selection of her poems through a queer lens, highlighting the poems&amp;rsquo; relationships to female love and Dickinson&amp;rsquo;s life and arguing against established patterns of erasing Dickinson&amp;rsquo;s queer identity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LITR 250 Close Reading 2E</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/litr-250-close-reading-2e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/litr-250-close-reading-2e/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the beginning of Chapter VIII in the third section of &lt;em&gt;To the Lighthouse&lt;/em&gt;, pages 186-187, Virginia Woolf&amp;rsquo;s unique approach to perspective and introspection create a subjective presentation of reality and relationships, supported by extended metaphors of fluidity and stillness. On a boat trip mandated by Mr. Ramsay to the titular lighthouse, Cam and James anatomize and unfold their feelings towards their father. Cam evolves as the boat moves across the sea while James&amp;rsquo;s unflinching rage and violence towards the patriarch repeat in this section as the sailboat halts and space contracts to exacerbate his indignation. Woolf thus frames and explores the figure of Mr. Ramsay and the nominal motif of a journey through individual introspection and excurses. &lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House of Leaves: Appendix II-E, The Three Attic Whalestoe Institute Letters (May 8th, 1987)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/house-of-leaves-appendix-ii-e-the-three-attic-whalestoe-institute-letters-may-8th-1987/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/house-of-leaves-appendix-ii-e-the-three-attic-whalestoe-institute-letters-may-8th-1987/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve picked up &lt;em&gt;House of Leaves&lt;/em&gt; again, Mark Z. Danielewski’s debut novel and veritable puzzle of a book. I previously abandoned it because, as a horror novel, I was having some trouble sleeping after reading it, but I’ve wanted to read it for years and the new year seems like a good time to conquer my fears.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s plenty of discussion around the internet regarding the book, and plenty more people who, I’m sure, have decoded the book’s many coded messages. But I’m a stingy sort who likes to do things on my own, and I thought I’d log some of it here! The first of my challenges was a letter from Appendix II-E, sent to Johnny Truant from his mother; she suspects that the director of the Whalestoe Institute, where she is institutionalized, is intercepting her letters. She is able to send a private letter to Johnny via an attendant, telling him the key to her next letter: take only the first letter of each word, separate those letters into something coherent, and find her true message (the letter itself is pure nonsense). Therefore, it’s no significant discovery on my part, but more of a fun first challenge. Warning that this is a book of psychological horror, and the contents below may be troubling or triggering (esp. for rape victims).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
